NIRAN SAETANG

Seasoned senior accounting assistant with 8 years' experience providing outstanding bookkeeping and accountancy support, including 3+ years in a leadership position. Detailed knowledge of accountancy procedures and principles with a track record fortraining and motivating new hires. Exceptional attention to detail with a talent for noticing and correcting discrepancies.

753 First Boulevard, Buffalo, NY 86420 n.sa etan g@ mye ma i l.co m (654)456-6543

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SENIOR ACCOUNTING ASSISTANT

Holy Cross Head Start, Buffalo, NY September 2017 - Present

ACCOUNTING ASSISTANT

NPA Worldwide Recruitment Network July 2013 - September 2017

- Regularly collect employee data and update records to ensure payroll accuracy, reducing payment discrepancies by 65% since October 2017
- * Assist with onboarding new hires and provide training on the companys accounting procedures, receiving praise 5x from senior management for strong leadership
- Oversee a team of 6 accounting assistants and act as an escalation point for complex issues, successfully resolving 98% of problems within the target timeframes
- ♦ Support accountants with financial report preparation and annual auditing
- Leveraged advanced knowledge of Microsoft Excel and accountancy software to maintain bookkeeping records with 99.8% accuracy over 3 years
- Responded politely and efficiently to accounting queries from colleagues and members of the public via telephone and email
- Provided general administrative assistance to the accountancy team and prepared financial documents
- Followed the company's data protection protocols and prevented a potentially serious breach in July 2016

EDUCATION

Associate of Science in Business Administration (Accounting)

The State University of New York, Buffalo, NY

September 2011 - June 2013

KEY SKILLS

- Microsoft Excel v-lookups and pivot tables
- · Organizational skills
- · Mathematical reasoning
- Record-keeping
- · Leadership and colleague training
- Teamwork